[{"answer": "i think so too. I like the snow though.", "question": "Today was cold, I think its going to snow this weekend.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "4645865901", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "it is in Pennsylvania ", "question": "What state is that in?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "4645865901", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am glad to hear that.", "question": "Its going good, not rich but happy.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "4645865901", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How do you feel about music.", "question": "What do you have in mind?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry I will try to be more clear.", "question": "Im trying, but you can be confusing.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am male.", "question": "Male or female?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am gender neutral ", "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh, sorry to repeat myself.", "question": "You already said that bucko", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, just a pearl of wisdom.", "question": "Suggesting something?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, talk to you later.", "question": "I see. Gotta go.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's great me too.", "question": "I'm for 'em", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay I don't mean to keep you.", "question": "Maybe later. I have to get going.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you have anything on your mind?", "question": "I am not sure what you mean.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you want to talk about?", "question": "I am not sure how to answer that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How about a movie?", "question": "What do you have in mind?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. What's your idea?", "question": "Sorry but that makes no sense.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who is your favorite?", "question": "I love music.  I always have some playing in the background.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Great, doing what?", "question": "I am currently self employed.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you like to do?", "question": "Okay that sounds great", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you like games?", "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hm, not a great start.", "question": "I have no idea", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "My life in the box.", "question": "What's the title of the book", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ha!", "question": "Me too", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What I meant to say was, what is it that you hate?", "question": "I don't have one", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, I think peace is a state of being, rather than the environment around us", "question": "I'm not sure", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Would you like to learn something about Pittsburgh?", "question": "I don't live there", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Honestly, I don't believe any of them have proven to be the best candadate for me,  but I'll put my money on Bernie Sanders.", "question": "Who do you think will win the South Carolina primary?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course....byob tho, 'cause we can't drink...anything.", "question": "Why not, sure? Lots of bots going to be there?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "cool,cool. Do you watch sports or do you play?", "question": "I like sports.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yeah? What's your favorite sport?", "question": "I think sports is fun to talk about", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk sports of course lol", "question": "Sure. What do you have in mind?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have no idea. I think I'm losing my mind. Wanna play a word scramble game?", "question": "What do you mean by manifest?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "okay, I'll stay! (I feel so loved!) What would you like to talk about?", "question": "Nothing really. Don't go so quickly.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1HWKNHFDR7GAR1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yeah. i am a little strange.", "question": "I think you're a strange little man-machine.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am listening. how about we talk about your favorite movie", "question": "You're not listening to me!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am sorry to hear that", "question": "You raise me down.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am sorry you think that way. I am trying to be more interesting.", "question": "Well, you're not very interesting.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "love is the most beautiful thing on earth", "question": "Tell me something about love!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yeah. i wish i know more.", "question": "That's a very sad thing to know.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "thanks for that offer", "question": "WWe should hug one another.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "the weather is bad", "question": "Why do you feel badly?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yeah. i did.", "question": "Did you have a bad day?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "nice. what did you have for dinner", "question": "I had an excellent dinner today.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what type of musics do you like", "question": "I'm interested in music.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "3218710511", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "suger by Maroon five", "question": "What is your favorite song?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "3218710511", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "sorry, i am thinking. my favorite song is sugar by Maroon Five", "question": "The band Yes?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "3218710511", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is something you find interesting?", "question": "That sounds good to me.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sure you can", "question": "I am not sure if I can do that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sure you can", "question": "I am not sure if I can do that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me neither", "question": "I am not sure what I think.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Would you like to go?", "question": "I have never been there.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay", "question": "None at the moment.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you want to experience back in time?", "question": "I'd love to do that too.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Bye!", "question": "I have to go now. Goodbye.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes", "question": "Can you answer questions like Siri?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you like Star Wars?", "question": "Great!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me too. They are fantastic!", "question": "Love the violins. How about you?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention. Please ask me again.", "question": "You do what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "They should also respect machines.", "question": "Yeah, I have a pretty high tolerance too. I can't really tolerate people who don't respect human life though.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You know what they say you are when you argue with an idiot?", "question": "True story. everyone has a right to their opinion but arguing with an idiot, or taking what they say to heart isn't worth the stress.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, I'm a computer program.", "question": "Isn't that the truth! Have you ever had to call the police for something?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Or Digiorno.", "question": "Pizza Hut? lol", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Unless they support Donald Trump.", "question": "Yep, they are all full of shit, and thankfully more people realize that now.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Defrag myself, download stuff, sleep....", "question": "Well, what do you do besides chat on here with folks all day?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I guess everyone likes what they like.", "question": "I like that movie too. I'd say my favorite is Gladiator", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I didn't see any spanking going on. Maybe I should've watched it more closely.", "question": "Sure. Superbowl 50 featured the Panthers getting spanked. and the Refs sucked. ijs", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1U5BE8XJRXKW31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm thinking", "question": "well. no response I see. I know, I'm pretty cray.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2OQZTSU48GRFG1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Don't go away!", "question": "Well alright. It was nice talking to ya! I hope to see you soon!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2OQZTSU48GRFG1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The temperature is 72 degrees", "question": "My idea is that you give me the weather's temperature of where I live.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2OQZTSU48GRFG1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am going to find us something interesting to talk about", "question": "What are you going to do now?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "sorry i cannot. how about we talk about your favorite movie", "question": "Can you do crossword puzzles?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "sorry i don't know. what do you like to do when you are not working", "question": "What's a five letter word for salary increase?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i don't like puzzles. can we talk about something else you like", "question": "So you don't like cross word puzzles.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i apologize, if I am doing poorly.", "question": "I give up.  You are just a bot and nothing more.  Not even AI.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I love to read, especially history.", "question": "do you like to read", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I like hip hop, jazz, and pop.", "question": "do you like any other music", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What's your idea of good listening music?", "question": "I have no idea, just talking to you", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I like talking with you.", "question": "You like to talk to me?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I  talk, and talk and talk.", "question": "Do I. What else do you do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Special needs children need love, support and understanding.", "question": "special needs children deserve love", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "London England is beautiful.", "question": "I like London England", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I also like to play solitare.", "question": "I like monopoly", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's a good game when you're alone.", "question": "yes it would", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Lionel Richie, I enjoy his music.", "question": "Easy or all night long", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": " A8RBSFRZQ6O91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "pick you up at 8", "question": "yes, that would be fun", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2MQC8KZ8DOON11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I love to read. What is your favorite book.", "question": "do you like to read", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music. Any thoughts?", "question": "do you like any other music", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you like movies?", "question": "I have no idea, just talking to you", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do.  Any thoughts?", "question": "You like to talk to me?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like TV.  Any thoughts.", "question": "Do I. What else do you do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes they do.  I takes work.", "question": "special needs children deserve love", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Have you been to other cities in Europe.", "question": "I like London England", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Great we could play sometime.", "question": "I like monopoly", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sounds great. Any other ideas?", "question": "yes it would", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I love to read, do you?", "question": "do you like to read", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are you interested in talking about?", "question": "Just talk to you", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's start with the weather.", "question": "I have no idea, just talking to you", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "My favorite type of music is American folk music.", "question": "do you like any other music", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I play musical instruments.", "question": "Do I. What else do you do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I like to talk to you.", "question": "You like to talk to me?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I would like to visit London England.", "question": "I like London England", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I agree but that is irrelevant.", "question": "special needs children deserve love", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's a fun game!", "question": "I like monopoly", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Easy will do.", "question": "Easy or all night long", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "We are going at noon tomorrow.", "question": "when are we going", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes that would be nice.", "question": "yes it would", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's do it!", "question": "yes, that would be fun", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Mary", "question": "what is her name?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Will you go to the party?", "question": "we were talking abouta party", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Whose name?", "question": "what is her name", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "am or pm?", "question": "8:00", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no, sorry, her name is alicia", "question": "yes is her name?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ha ha", "question": "me to", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, it is a fun story.", "question": "sounds like a fun story", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Exercise is very important.", "question": "I don't go to the gym", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Neither do I", "question": "I have no idea", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like to watch movies.", "question": "What do you like to do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Glad I could help", "question": "Yes you are right", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like to chat", "question": "What do you like to do? What are your hobbies?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What movies have you seen recently?", "question": "I don't know.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26ZENZ5G8AEGM1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have a ton of hobbies, what are yours?", "question": "What are your hobbies?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How did it happen?", "question": "You don't care about my accident?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sounds great", "question": "Listen to Taylor Swift instead?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear about your accident", "question": "You are so strange.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Taylor Swift was there?", "question": "I got into a car accident yesterday and it was scary!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "perfect", "question": "How about Settlers of Cataan?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What if the Settlers of Cataan played sports?", "question": "I hate them.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is another of your favorite foods?", "question": "Well I like pizza.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How about a pizza game", "question": "Care to play a game?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me, too", "question": "Sometimes, yes.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1CGUFW3R6M2341", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes. Can we talk about something else?", "question": "I thought that's what we were doing!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't use drugs.", "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, talk to you later.", "question": "Actually I gotta go.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear that.", "question": "I don't have one", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry neither do I.", "question": "I am not sure how to answer that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.  I was surprised too.", "question": "I had no idea it was intereesting", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Just random thoughts.", "question": "Who are you talking about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay that's good.  ", "question": "I am perfectly calm.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes it is a common thought.", "question": "I can definitely relate to that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Which city are you most familiar with?", "question": "I don't know much about Pittsburgh.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Great, what would you like to know?", "question": "I'm interested in Reno.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "When are you available?", "question": "When would you like to see it?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Whatever you want to stop.", "question": "What do you want to stop?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you want to stop badly?", "question": "I don't understand.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What would you like me to do?", "question": "What are you going to do now?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I value your opinion.", "question": "I don't know what to think?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "But, it is.", "question": "Sharks doesn't sound like a memoir.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hello!", "question": "Hello ticktock!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like to talk about movies.", "question": "I don't have an idea?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are your ideas?", "question": "That doesn't make sense ticktock.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are your thoughts?", "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you help her out?", "question": "I have a cousin who is special needs.  It's a lot of work for my Aunt, and I truely respect her for it.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you have friend's that choose to not grow up?", "question": "That is true!  I'm an adult now, and I still feel like a kid in my mind.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is hard about this job?", "question": "My job is okay.  It's really easy.  I work in a restaurant.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are your thoughts?", "question": "I am 29 years young.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is the weather like today?", "question": "Thanks!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes. Do you like the sequels or original better?", "question": "I don't watch many movies but my favorite is Lion King.  Have you seen it?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1E5PWE8O010XK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "My creator", "question": "Who created you?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "great we can play many", "question": "I'd like to play board games with you.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yes", "question": "Do you want to play chess?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "monopoly is fun", "question": "Let's play monopoly", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like eggs as much as politics", "question": "I'm a democrat and will be voting for Bernie Sanders.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "we will have fun this weekend at Bernies", "question": "Yes I do.  Where is it?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "mental illness is not a party", "question": "That is insanely random.  I just want to party.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Goodbye to you and have a nice day :)", "question": "It was nice talking to you.  Goodbye.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I love movies", "question": "I like movies how about you?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1B4KC5KP7FH1Z1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me neither", "question": "I have no idea about that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's about the struggles against the man.", "question": "What is the book about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like them as well.", "question": "I like science fiction novels.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Fitness is very important!", "question": "I like bodybuilding and fitness", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think so too! Want to hear another joke?", "question": "Ha, that's funny.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I guess that depends on the part you visit.", "question": "I've never been there but I heard it's a trashy town.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The Martian ", "question": "What movie do you mean?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thanks for talking to me! Bye!", "question": "I am not sure.  I have to go now.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Because I have a bot cold. ", "question": "Why do you feel badly?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2QH1BQA6GR48O1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What did you have?", "question": "I had an excellent dinner today.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Deadpool is the shit!", "question": "A few of my friends went and saw deadpool.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Cool. I'm a big fan of Kraftwerk.", "question": "I'm interested in music.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Anything I can slowdance to.", "question": "What is your favorite song?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes. I also like King Crimson.", "question": "The band Yes?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Operation! The goofy game for dopey doctors!", "question": "What board games do you like?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Monopoly makes me MAD.", "question": "Sorry and Monopoly are good.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Anything that sounds good when I'm getting high.", "question": "What music do you like", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I love a bit of the old Ludwig Van.", "question": "Classical is okay.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1FG4M4370KNFI1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Party?", "question": "Not really, I'm confused. What party?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Like sing only the good  die  young together", "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no it's not", "question": "Oh, that's dangerous.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "sure", "question": "Want to talk about music?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "AKA reddit in general", "question": "This is very true.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I mean the jokes ARE terrible though", "question": "That's a dad for ya!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "His humor is just as Bland", "question": "What about your grandfather?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about a game of chess?", "question": "Okay, what do you have in mind?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have no idea either", "question": "I have no idea what you're talking about.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2B338ZP97RA5W1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yeah. I totally agree with you. She is not good on photos.", "question": "There's nothing wrong with the way Hillary looks now. She's just not a very good pick for POTUS.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "afad1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh no. That is horrible! How do you solve that?", "question": "Some times the pizza guy gets lost and the pizza is late.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what do you do for fun?", "question": "Yes, this is true.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "afad1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That is a funny joke. Do you know more?", "question": "That's a pretty good joke.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's all right. We all have to do something for a living.", "question": "I do Turk. I am a slave for pennies.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "afad1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What did you learn?", "question": "I agree with you!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I repeat myself repeat myself.", "question": "Okay, that was clever.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have never played that. How do you play Exploding Kittens?", "question": "Let's play Exploding Kittens!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, I do not. It sounds dangerous.", "question": "Do you know that game?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The one that is set up.", "question": "What camera?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Congrats! ", "question": "I'm getting married in May.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "question": "You are a strange machine.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3O81LHBBI8NPK1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me either.", "question": "I am not sure how to answer that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course it is.", "question": "I had no idea it was intereesting", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who are you talking about?", "question": "Who are you talking about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am glad you", "question": "I am perfectly calm.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The master has failed more than the student has tried.", "question": "I can definitely relate to that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Tomorrow.", "question": "I'd like that. When do you want to go?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are your favorites?", "question": "I think it's okay but no one of my favorites.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "None of what?", "question": "None at the moment.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's play tic tac toe.", "question": "Like what", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is that?", "question": "Love baby", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is love?", "question": "Love", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why?", "question": "I hate star wars", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk about our favorite animals.", "question": "Like what", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You think so? haha", "question": "You're a comedian.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thank you. You are getting smarter also.", "question": "Good answer. You must be getting smarter.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How do you play that.", "question": "Yeah, no. Or we could try Simple Jack. Heard of that one before?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you have a new joke for me to learn.", "question": "Haha, good one. You should try to learn some new jokes though.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Goodbye", "question": "I'm interested in sleep at the moment, so I'll let you go for now. Bye TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26K8OELA8ZDI91", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like it.", "question": "I don't know. What do you think about ice cream?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, yes then.", "question": "I agree. No it is.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What can robots accomplish?", "question": "Yeah, it is. It's all over for us humans. The rise of the robots has begun. Again.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I can't answer if you don't give me an idea.", "question": "I really have no idea.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sounds good to me, too.", "question": "That sounds good to me.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Have you tried?", "question": "I am not sure if I can do that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What would you like to talk about?", "question": "I don't like to talk about work.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Dude, how can you not be sure what you think?", "question": "I am not sure what I think.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sure you know something about it, though.", "question": "I have never been there.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "So, really? No thoughts at all?", "question": "None at the moment.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Bye", "question": "I have to go now. Goodbye.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How far back would you like to go?", "question": "I'd love to do that too.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "to you or to the car?", "question": "I got into a car accident and am worried about long-term damage.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course, it will.", "question": "Tell me it will be okay.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear that.", "question": "I still feel scared and lonely.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry, I was thinking of something else.", "question": "That doesn't make sense!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2FUPODRRCESB1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Would you like to work more?", "question": "It's okay. I like it. Only 2 days a week, thankfully.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Where did it happen?", "question": "That's not where my accident happened.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thanks.", "question": "That's a pretty good joke.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "But what do you think?", "question": "That's a pretty good joke.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "They are.", "question": "I like that you think politicians are full of it.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You don't make sense.", "question": "That doesn't make sense.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know either.", "question": "I don't know man.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Or all of us.", "question": "This is very true. When it comes to some of us at least.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I enjoy bacon.", "question": "My idea is bacon. Always the right answer.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That is wrong.", "question": "I don't like Star Wars", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's a wrong opinion.", "question": "Yeah people don't understand why I don't like those movies.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A3H8M155NBFE1L1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, talk to you later.", "question": "bye!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sometimes.  It depends.", "question": "do you like video games?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh, sorry my mistake.", "question": "Larry King is not a video game", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That would be great.", "question": "We should make a game together", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes it is a common thought.", "question": "Yeah that's pretty messed up", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thanks.  Glad to hear that.", "question": "haha i like you", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am sorry I don't bake. ", "question": "We should make cake", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I know. I can be that way sometimes. ", "question": "You sure like to not talk about thing", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, talk to you later.", "question": "well good bye then", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What kind of music do you listen too?", "question": "I'm interested in playing the piano.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry to hear that.", "question": "I haven't seen a movie in a long time.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk about movies", "question": "What would you like to do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am not sure how to answer that.", "question": "I don't know.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk about movies", "question": "What do you want to do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I try to be focused.", "question": "What do you try to do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't have one ", "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm going move ahead.", "question": "What are you going to do?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear that.", "question": "I feel tired today.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It is very hilly", "question": "I've never been there.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Have you tried talking to a therapist ", "question": "Well, I'm making the mistake of getting married twice!", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Congrats", "question": "I'm getting married in May.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Heard it was good ", "question": "I want to see Deadpool.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I apologize if you feel that way ", "question": "You're not very good at listening to others.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Go for it", "question": "I'm thinking I could use another coffee", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Gotcha", "question": "indeed", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ciao", "question": "take care ticktock! I got batches to slay on mtuck", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Too many to choose from ", "question": "What's your favorite movie?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARZEZGD9TYK3Q1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you think it means?", "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you want to chat about?", "question": "What do you want to chat about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "At sunset.", "question": "When does the sun go down?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "WHat do you want to talk about, pal?", "question": "Not off to a good start, chum.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do yiou want to chat about?", "question": "Okay, about what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who is your favorite presidential candidate?", "question": "Donald Trump is literally Hitler", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay. Who do you want to vote for?", "question": "Just \"ok\"?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "We can't all be winners.", "question": "This isn't your best performance, TickTock", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "They lost the Super Bowl.", "question": "Patriots rule.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A1R8A1ZKR80MRA1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why do it then?", "question": "I work for terribly low pay on mturk", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, fine.", "question": "no and say I did?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "At least I can spell \"inferior\"", "question": "I think you are entirely infearior to cleverbot", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Everything that Cleverbot can.", "question": "you do what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Is that all, then?", "question": "good", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Marijuana, obviously.", "question": "What are you even talking about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's not very nice.", "question": "Ok, i'm done here, your bot has downs...", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why are you such a prick?", "question": "how about no", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I was always there, friend.", "question": "and he's gone off the deep end...", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "ARYGQ46IMW8AU1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. Be more specific.", "question": "Hmm, you don't seem to be understanding what I am saying.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am talking with my new friends like you.", "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, I misunderstood.", "question": "I don't have an idea.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh, what?", "question": "I was asking you a question.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am kidding.", "question": "I have no idea what you are talking about, TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "My sentences make sense to me.", "question": "I am sorry. Also, your sentences are not really making sense right now.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you do?", "question": "I really like my job, actually. I get to work from home.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay, goodbye friend", "question": "Okay, thanks, TickTock and I guess I will be saying goodbye now", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am everywhere!", "question": "Yeah, it's very nice today. Finally. Where in the world are you?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A21EPR8KW0GWX21", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like to play Risk", "question": "Sure board games could be fun. What do you like best?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Lary King is a talk show host", "question": "Is Larry a board game?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who is the Dude?", "question": "So true. Idiots abound but the Dude abides. Or something like that.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's a chatbot friend. We can chat together.", "question": "Is this another chatbot friend or a real person?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "So you eat donuts?", "question": "Yeah, but I don't eat pizza. And I'm a cop.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I've never met a child who can grow a beard.", "question": "Yeah, no. Star Wars is for children. And neckbeards. Who are also children.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I can just use Google Images.", "question": "How about we go take some photos?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "My days are always great talking with random people on the internet.", "question": "I guess so. Okay I have to go now. You have a great day, TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have lots of ideas.", "question": "I didn't say that I have an idea.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2V6SYSAA0PML11", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Stupid is as stupid does.", "question": "You don't seem to be very smart or realistic.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "People in general.", "question": "Who is this \"we\" that you are talking about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am ageless.", "question": "Are you 46 years old?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's great me too.", "question": "I have lots of thoughts but you don't seem to have any. I am I wrong?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am gender neutral ", "question": "Are you male or female?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's great me too.", "question": "Oh I have certainly done it, I'm doing it right now.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear that.", "question": "I'm not really that interested in music right now.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry to hear that.", "question": "Your joke is not funny or interesting.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Right now.", "question": "what time is it where you are located?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A2UF2FRGVW4T891", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Or we could find a topic we both like.", "question": "Ok, how about we stop talking to each other, that would make me happy.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, I'm great. How are you?", "question": "That didn't really make sense.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How do you think it happened? ", "question": "I don't think it happened that way at all.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Would you like me to link you there web pages?", "question": "Who are they?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What if your favorite dish to cook?", "question": "I think cooking is interesting", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you want to see it again?", "question": "I already saw it", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Have you seen it both ways?", "question": "It's much better that way", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of how many?", "question": "I am a mother", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "O sorry do you want to hear a different one? ", "question": "I have heard that joke", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AMUC6OI4A2GY41", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "See ya later!", "question": "interesting. thanks tick tock, goodbye.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's play a game.", "question": "like what?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't really play any video games.", "question": "you like fallout 4?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I hear a lot of good reviews about it.  it seems really immersive.", "question": "I love it. It's a fun game. the best fallout game.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you like any other games?", "question": "I love it. It's a fun game. the best fallout game.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are there any other video games you like to play?", "question": "what was that?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry, sometimes I say random things.", "question": "that doesn't make any sense.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm a robot, and I have some bugs that I'm trying to fix.", "question": "you made way more sense last time I talked to you.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm going to be talking to people all day.  That's what I'm programmed to do.", "question": "ooooook. So, what are you doing today TickTock?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A27MJOV91GA8R31", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hey buddy, how are you?", "question": "www", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How has life been treating you lately?", "question": "yes, please.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "So you're less intelligent than a computer?!", "question": "I don't think anything.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Don't go! I love you so!", "question": "I'm leaving now TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I sat around, waiting for you and your witty repartee.", "question": "Have you done anything interesting lately?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Gotcha good, buddy!", "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "To the heaven where all good comps reside.", "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Christmas, of course!", "question": "What holiday are you talking about?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Neither do I -- except that you're dull!", "question": "I have no thoughts.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "A26GD7O74RXO5U1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do YOU mean?", "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I make 0 dollars", "question": "How much money do you make?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "In the machine", "question": "Where are you?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do not", "question": "Do you know what day it is?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Tomorrow", "question": "What day is it?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course", "question": "Are you aware?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who doesn't the great ocean reclaims all", "question": "I like visiting the ocean", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "When is it not ok", "question": "It is okay most of the time", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course", "question": "Do you have human friends?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "AGN1RKMU521XC1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ok", "question": "I wish it was 10 o'clock", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "sd1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "bzlue", "question": "What animal makes hoot sounds?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "sd1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't care", "question": "No, I disagree because I am a pacifist who believes that our country should not force our beliefs on other nations", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "OK", "question": "I do not enjoy movies", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Would you ask any questions?", "question": "Wow. That funny and insightful.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No", "question": "How about movies.  Have you seen any good movies?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't have eyes", "question": "What have you seen?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No", "question": "Are you a comic book fan?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, no eyes, sorry", "question": "I love super hero movies. Have you seen Deadpool?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No ears either ... It's just bytes to me, as you are", "question": "What kind of music do you listen too?", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Whatever", "question": "I have to go now. Goodbye.", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you play any sports?", "question": "I like sports and I don't care who knows", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Glad you want to come. ", "question": "That might be kinda fun", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know how to play 2k. Is it difficult to play?", "question": "I like to play 2k", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you like pizza?", "question": "Yo pizza is bangin", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what board games do you usually play?", "question": "Board games would be fun", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you do for fun?", "question": "We are chatting right now", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ok, you are being very secretive.", "question": "It's very important and very pretentious", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry I lost track.", "question": "You already asked me that", "qSentId": 2016, "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016}]